Guide to the Alger Hiss Family Papers TAM.314
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Non-Microfilmed Correspondence and Subject Files, 1931-2003
  - Savoy, Prew: Philadelphia Retail Meat Dealers Association, Philadelphia (speech), Nov 20, 1933 (Box 7A, Folder 17)
  - Tiger, Edith: Correspondence, re: Alger Hiss, 1996-1997 (Box 7A, Folder 18)
  - United Nations: Conference and Secretariat Personnel, Apr 1945-May 1945 (Box 7A, Folder 19)
  - United States Department of Agriculture: Memorandum to Chester C. Davis, Administrator, Feb 4, 1935 (Box 7A, Folder 20)
  - Vassiliev, Alexander: Court Case, Jun 2003 (Box 7A, Folder 21)
  - Volkogonov, Dmitry: Controversy, 1992 (Box 7A, Folder 22)
  - Wheelock, Charles H.: Agreement and Declaration (Property Ownership), 1931 (Box 7A, Folder 23)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: Alger Hiss Project, First of Three Films [missing or misplaced as of 7/2/2010], undated (Box 7A, Folder 24)
- Series V: Non-Microfilmed Correspondence and Subject Files from the Alger Hiss Collection at Harvard University, Photocopies, 1934-2000
  - Correspondence, 1910s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, [1965] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, [1973] (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1963-Jul 1963 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1974-Mar 1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1974-Jul 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, [1975] (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1975-Mar 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1975-Sep 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, [1976] (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1976-Mar 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1977-May 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, [1978] (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1978-May 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, [1979] (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, [1980] (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1980-May 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, [1981] (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Mar 1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1981-Jul 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Fansler Family Tree, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hiss, Alger: FBI File (Redacted), 1940s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hiss, Alger: Fletcher and Weslar Cases, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hiss, Alger: Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Alger: Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hiss, Alger: Henry Carter, re:, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hiss, Alger: International Trade Acts and Agreements, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hiss, Alger: International Trade Duties, 1936-1937, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hiss, Alger: International Trade/Tariffs, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hiss, Alger: League of Nations, 1930s (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hiss, Alger: Manuscripts, re:, 1960s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Hiss, Alger: Maritime Agreements, 1910s-1930s (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Hiss, Alger: Memoranda, 1930s (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hiss, Alger: Petroleum and Natural Resources Policy, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Alger: The Philippines, re:, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hiss, Alger: Presentations, re:, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Hiss, Alger: Prison Record and Penitentiaries, 1940s-1950s (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Hiss, Alger: Robert Johnson, re:, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hiss, Alger: U.S. Department of Justice, Office of the Solicitor General, 1930s (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hiss, Alger: Writings, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Hobson, Timothy: Correspondence, 1951-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Department of State: Division of Trade Agreements, 1930s (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Zeligs, Meyer: Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Series VI: Grand Jury Testimony, 1947-1949
  - Grand Jury Testimony, Index, 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 849-887, Jul 22, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 967-1001, Jul 31, 1947-Nov 24, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 2425-2559, Nov 24, 1947-Nov 25, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 2560-2755 (Includes Alger Hiss), Dec 3, 1947-Mar 25, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 2756-2995 (Includes Harry Dexter White), Mar 30, 1948-Apr 7, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 2996-3500, Apr 7, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 3501-3718 (Includes Whittaker Chambers and Alger Hiss), Dec 6, 1948-Dec 8, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 3719-3981 (Includes Alger and Priscilla Hiss), Dec 8, 1948-Dec 10, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 3982-4126 (Includes Whittaker Chambers and Alger Hiss), Dec 10, 1948-Dec 13, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 4127-4433 (Includes Alger Hiss and Richard Nixon), Dec 13, 1948-Dec 14, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 4434-4701 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Dec 15, 1948-Dec 20, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 4702-4987 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Dec 21, 1948-Jan 4, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 4988-5217, Jan 4, 1949-Jan 11, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 5218-5458 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Jan 11, 1949-Jan 19, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 5459-5722 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Jan 19, 1949-Jan 26, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 5723-6051 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Jan 26, 1949-Feb 9, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 6052-6277 (Includes Whittaker Chambers), Feb 9, 1949-Feb 15, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 6278-6453, Feb 17, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 7023-7209, Apr 12, 1949-Apr 19, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Grand Jury Testimony, pp. 7241-7429 (Includes Representative Karl E. Mundt and Richard Nixon), May 5, 1949-May 17, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Photographs, circa 1906-2001
  - Family Portraits, circa 1906-1952; undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Negatives: Strip of 35mm negative film (still), undated (Box 15)
  - Portraits, 1971-1978; undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Postcards: Carrington House (Rhode Island School of Design), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Slides: Hiss; Lowenthal, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Slides: Hiss Lecture, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Website Launch: "Alger Hiss Story", Mar 21, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Website Launch: "Alger Hiss Story" Display I, Mar 21, 2001 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS006, Folder 1)
  - Website Launch: "Alger Hiss Story" Display II, Mar 21, 2001 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS006, Folder 2)
  - Group photo (Box Shared Tamiment 032)